c: 949.394.7633 | cmarie0518@msn.com | http://linkedin.com/in/connieglover/ | Dallas

ABOUT

An accomplished marketing communications, content, P.R., and sales leader who enjoys bringing visibility to companies and brands to life. I get you noticed with grass-roots efforts and current digital best practices. I understand all stakeholder groups and how to engage them through effective communications strategies. I specialize in finding unique ways to draw on my project management and marketing skills and am often tapped to participate in projects in addition to the scope of my initial requirements. I use strong analytical skills to find customer-focused solutions that lead to sustainable growth and solid retention rates.

■ Resourceful Problem-solving	■ Public Relations/Earned Media	Multinational Project Mgmt
Omnichannel Campaigns	■ Content Creation (digital/print)	■ Crisis Communications
■ Corporate Communications	■ Executive-level Consulting	■ B2B and B2C Marketing
■ Demand Generation	■ GTM Strategist	■ ABM + Product-led Mktg

RELEVANT PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

TRAVA—*Indianapolis, Indiana (remote)*

June 2021 –present

Content Marketing and Demand Gen

Trava is a cybersecurity and cyber insurance company that exists to protect small and medium-size businesses from the potential damage of cyber threats, by integrating assessment, mitigation, and insurance into one convenient cyber risk management platform.

- Drive brand awareness and engagement by publishing compelling content for live events, speaking engagements, investor pitches, blogs, educational papers, and Forbes articles
- Produce email marketing campaigns, with average open rates of 30%
- Produce, budget, and execute company's GTM demand gen plan
- Oversee team of content marketers, designers, web administrators
- Establishe KPIs and metrics for analyzing demand gen success
- Sales training on sales enablement tools and social selling

TEAMSUPPORT—Dallas, Texas

March 2020 -June 2021

VP, Communications and Product Marketing

TeamSupport is a multiple award-winning, cloud-based B2B customer support software solution provider. Executive-level marketing communications leadership and tactical contributions that included:

Driving brand awareness through compelling content across all channels.

1

c: 949.394.7633 | cmarie0518@msn.com | http://linkedin.com/in/connieglover/ | Dallas

- Reversed churn trends (by \$100K Q4 over Q3) and increased upsell opportunities by executing new customer engagement strategies.
- Enabling greater percentages of net new logo closed and shortened time to close with a robust library of new sales enablement tools.
- Increased year over year lead generation 210%; lower funnel sales conversions 52%, website traffic 173%, and optimized footprint across all digital channels.
- Launching multi-stage persona-driven buyer journey nurture sequences based on ideal client profile and addressable target market.
- Producing over 200 pieces of thought leadership content, new logo development, extensive sales enablement tools, social media campaigns, webinars, and customer engagement communication campaigns.

Direct reports: Director content marketing and social media manager

YOOZ, INC.—Dallas, Texas

Aug 2017-March 2020

Marketing Communications and Product Marketing

Yooz is a global, multiple award-winning, cloud-based AP (accounts payable) solution provider. Executive-level marketing communications consult, leadership, and tactical contributions that included:

KEY ACCOMPLISHMENTS:

- Drove brand recognition by earning nine industry awards and recognitions in 18 months.
- Established Yooz as a thought-leader in the accounts payable automation and advanced technologies spaces by: publishing original content distinguished media outlets in the finance and accounting space, such as *Hospitality Technology, Accounting Today*, the Sage Intacct blog, *The EA (Enrolled Agent) Journal*, and Finance Executives International *FEI Daily*; producing more than 150 original thought-leadership content blogs, articles, and success stories on the topics of FinTech, finance and accounting operations, and emerging technologies each year.
- Increased demand indicated by examples such as: Email engagement and open rates increased by 335.35%; direct website traffic increased by 166.98%; increase in social media traffic by 188.73% in Q2 2019.
- Created and activated more than 50+ buyer's journey persona-driven nurture sequences and several hundred pieces of thought leadership content including use cases, white papers, blogs, and social media content.
- Designed and implemented omni-channel marketing campaigns, nurture, and engagement programs.
- Increased year over year sales 138%, lead generation 32%, sales conversion 9%, and velocity 34%. Tripled web, social channel traffic, followers, and impressions, and launched a sales enablement platform.
- Project managed (including story board creation, interview questions, and talent management) for two segments on <u>Worldwide Business with Kathy Ireland</u> aired on global networks such as *Bloomberg Global* and *Fox Business*.

c: 949.394.7633 | cmarie0518@msn.com | http://linkedin.com/in/connieglover/ | Dallas

WORLDVENTURES—*Plano, Texas*

Oct 2015-Oct 2016

Public Relations, Brand + Foundation

WorldVentures is the leading direct seller of lifestyle and travel club memberships operating in 29 countries. Managed Public Relations for the WorldVentures Holdings entities and the WorldVentures Foundation and contributed to P.R. for technology collaboration with publicly-traded NXT-ID:

- Earned media placements in local print and television news outlets for every WorldVentures Foundation event and placements on major digital business outlets for corporate news releases.
- Designed and implemented new Corporate Responsibility and Sustainability initiative, engaging participation of all departments.
- Designed and implemented new corporate crisis communications plan in collaboration with Chief Counsel.
- Garnered positive P.R. for all corporate entities, resulting in an overall shift from negative to positive sentimenton reputation management reports.
- Managed TV segment for programming on Lifetime network highlighting WorldVentures Foundation
- Executive talent management and celebrity spokesperson management for on-camera and print interviews/appearances.

Manager quotable from Q2 2016 Performance Review: "Connie has an excellent ability to take complex information and communicate it to a variety of audiences."

DEALERTRACK, INC.—*Dallas, TX* (now subsidiary of Cox Automotive) **Oct 2013–Aug 2015 Product Marketing**

Dealertrack provides software solutions for the automotive industry. Served three Dealertrack business units: Inventory+, Digital Marketing, and CRM. Collaborated with SMEs (subject matter experts) on content development and quality control. Notable projects included:

- Customer engagement strategies and content to reduce churn: Initiated, designed, produced, and deployed two new business-to-auto dealer communications programs—The Driver's Seat biweekly product update and The Driver's Seat Quarterly Report industry newsletter—for each of three business units.
- Produced robust sales enablement tools and sales campaigns, such as: animated sales training tool, battle cards, and sales communications materials; including development of product marketing campaigns and print/digital brochures and information sheets.
- Initiated and managed new customer round table with key clients and OEMs gaining valuable VoC insight and input for product development.

General key accomplishment: Team's campaign marketing and P.R. efforts resulted in **new sales of \$4M** in 18-month period and a reversal of churn.

c: 949.394.7633 | cmarie0518@msn.com | http://linkedin.com/in/connieglover/ | Dallas

PROFESSIONAL AFFILIATIONS

Success North Dallas, https://successnorthdallas.com/

Pavilion (formerly Revenue Collective), Executive, https://www.revenuecollective.com/

CERTIFICATIONS

Certified Digital Marketing Professional, Digital Marketing Institute (in collaboration with American Marketing Association)

EDUCATION

PURDUE UNIVERSITY—online through main campus, West Lafayette, Indiana Graduate Certificate, Strategic Communications Management

ARIZONA STATE UNIVERSITY—Tempe, Arizona

Masters Certificate in Sustainability Technology Management

UNIVERSITY OF TEXAS, EL PASO—El Paso, Texas Bachelor of Business Administration, Marketing

I'm a storyteller. And I'm good at it. I learned from the best in the business, compelling writers and serious editors. This has allowed me to excel at the marketing communications, P.R., and content marketing parts of marketing. It has also inspired me to pay it forward, guiding others about how to write great stuff that get people interested in a product or service.

I got my start representing high profile academics who wanted to build their personal brands—this included promoting books they authored. I saw how my clients struggled with rejections from typical publishers and the complexity and expense of trying to publish themselves. I come to you with an understanding of your ICP and years in SaaS.